Y-You want to have
a five-day fuckathon?!
Yes.
Is there any better way
to spend your five days of vacation?
But what about things like eating?
We wouldn't be doing it nonstop.
For instance, we'd start with...
Hugging,
and simply holding hands.
We'll spend four days entirely on foreplay
and save the main event for the very end.
I think that would make for a lovely vacation.
Ah, I see.
Nadeshiko, would it make you happy if we did that?
Of course.
All right, then. Let's give it a try.
Okay!
DAY
We'll start with a day of slowly sharing our affection.
She pinned me against the wall?
No one's ever cornered me like this before.
It's kinda...
It's kinda cute.
DAY
This is different from how we usually make out.
Is kissing all we're doing today?
Yes.
I wasn't quite sure what to expect at first,
but taking it slow like this isn't so bad.
DAY
N-Nadeshiko!
You said we were saving this for the very end!
Well, touching below the waist
is off-limits for today,
so I'm helping myself to your top half instead.
Nadeshiko! Come on!
All right! That's enough for today.
We're saving the climax
for the final day, remember?
Huh? But...
I'm too horny to fall asleep!
DAY
Shall we focus on your lower body today?
Huh?!
For example,
the groin,
stroking your tummy,
or teasing you with my fingers.
I knew it. She's just going to work me up again.
If it feels this good now,
what on earth is tomorrow gonna be like?
DAY
Final Day
Now then,
are you ready to begin, Akane?
I've been so unfulfilled, I can't even sleep!
All right.
If I may, then.
All that from just one finger?!
Um, Akane?
Sorry for making you wait so long,
but I need you to hold on just a little longer, okay?
Huh?!
Right now, the slightest stimulation
can cause incredible pleasure.
So let's take our time so you can get used to it.
Nadeshiko...
Yes?
Nadeshiko!
It'll be all right.
Nadeshiko...
I just want you to feel as good as possible.
Hey, Akane...
You don't have to hold back anymore.
Feel free to tell me what you want me to do.
M-More...
I just need more!
Okay.
I'm working from home tomorrow...
Oh, I'm so sorry! Did I overdo it?
Regardless, I'm so happy right now.
I feel like I've finally fulfilled my purpose.
Nadeshiko...
Yes! Just like a washing machine or a microwave!
Uh...
Nadeshiko sure says some
robotic things from time to time.
She obviously seems fond of me,
but is that just her sexbot programming?
I love it...
I get to keep hearing you call me by my name.
Every time I hear you say "Nadeshiko,"
it makes me feel so good inside.
I'm so glad I got to hear it so many times today.
Sure thing.
I guess...
I don't need to overthink things for now.